<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hugo on Positiva - Echo notes &#43; news</title>
    <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hugo on Positiva - Echo notes &#43; news</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://positiva.netlify.app/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to become a better human</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/how-to-become-a-better-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/how-to-become-a-better-human/</guid>
      <description>How to Become a Better Human Becoming a better human involves a constant quest for self-improvement, not only for our own sake but for the collective good. Embracing empathy, practicing mindfulness, and cultivating kindness are just a few steps on this transformative journey. Through introspection and action, we delve into the practices that allow us to transcend our limitations and make meaningful contributions to the world around us.
Embrace Empathy: One of the cornerstones of becoming a better human is cultivating empathy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature is Magic</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/nature-is-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/nature-is-magic/</guid>
      <description>Nature is Magic In a world dominated by the empirical and the logical, a realm of enchantment lies just beyond our grasp—within the embrace of nature itself. Nature&amp;rsquo;s profound allure transcends mere science, speaking to something deeper within us. From the vibrant, ephemeral hues of a sunrise to the mesmerizing dance of fireflies in the moonlit night, the natural world whispers secrets that stir our souls. It is as if the very fabric of existence holds threads of enchantment that weave through the tapestry of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human is Not the Enemy</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/human-is-not-the-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/human-is-not-the-enemy/</guid>
      <description>Human is Not the Enemy While humanity&amp;rsquo;s impact on the environment is undeniable, painting humans as the sole enemy ignores the potential for positive change. Inherent within us is the power to heal, restore, and protect. Through innovation, collaboration, and conscious choices, we can mend the scars on the Earth&amp;rsquo;s surface and foster a harmonious coexistence with nature. By recognizing our capacity for positive impact, we embark on a journey toward ecological harmony and a shared future where humanity is a force for good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Places for Known Nature</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/risk-of-extinction-species/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/risk-of-extinction-species/</guid>
      <description>Amid the bustling cities and modern landscapes, pockets of pristine nature remain, offering refuge for weary souls seeking solace. These better places—whether hidden urban oases or remote wilderness sanctuaries—are where the beauty of the natural world flourishes. From the serene stillness of ancient forests to the vibrant energy of coral reefs, these places remind us of our intrinsic connection to the Earth. By venturing beyond the familiar, we discover the true treasures that nature has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Positiva is the new positive</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/positiva-is-the-new-positive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/positiva-is-the-new-positive/</guid>
      <description>Positiva is the new positive In a world driven by change, positivity emerges as a guiding light. As we navigate the complexities of modern living, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that every small action has the potential to create a significant impact.
Finding Balance At the heart of our journey is the pursuit of ecological harmony. We believe that positivity can be channeled into sustainability, and that each step toward a greener world is a step toward a brighter future.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
