<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Positiva World [notes &#43; news]</title>
    <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Positiva World [notes &#43; news]</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Awakening the Positive; An Ecological Journey</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/awakening-the-positive-an-ecology-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/awakening-the-positive-an-ecology-journey/</guid>
      <description>In our journey toward a more ecological world, we firmly believe that positivity can be a magical brush. Every environmentally friendly gesture, no matter how small, contributes to a significant impact on our planet. From reducing waste to adopting sustainable practices in our daily lives, each positive choice adds up, creating a healthier environment for future generations.
## Sustainability at the Heart of Our Focus
At Positive, we embrace the idea that positivity can be channeled into sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Better Human Being</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/how-to-become-a-better-human-being/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/how-to-become-a-better-human-being/</guid>
      <description>How to Become a Better Human Being Becoming a better human being involves a constant pursuit of self-improvement, not just for our own well-being but for the collective good. Embracing empathy, practicing mindfulness, and cultivating kindness are just a few steps in this transformative journey.
Through introspection and action, we delve into practices that allow us to transcend our limitations and make meaningful contributions to the world around us.
Embracing Empathy: One of the pillars of becoming a better human being is cultivating empathy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature for the New Generations</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/nature-for-the-new-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/nature-for-the-new-generation/</guid>
      <description>Nature for New Generations As modern society becomes increasingly driven by technology, the gap between children and the natural world widens. With the proliferation of digital devices and entertainment options, many young minds are captivated by virtual realities, often disconnected from the tangible beauty of the Earth.
This disconnection from nature not only robs children of the intrinsic joy of exploring the outdoors but also hampers their ability to comprehend the delicate balance that sustains life on our planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overpopulation is a Myth</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/overpopulation-is-a-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/overpopulation-is-a-myth/</guid>
      <description>Overpopulation is a Myth Ignoring Crucial Progress The concept of overpopulation overlooks advancements in areas such as education and access to contraception. Addressing global challenges requires a holistic understanding that goes beyond simplistic population equations, urging us to focus on sustainable practices and equitable distribution of resources.
A Misguided Approach The notion of overpopulation, positing that the world&amp;rsquo;s population will eventually surpass the planet&amp;rsquo;s capacity to sustain it, has captivated the collective imagination for decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature is Magical</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/nature-is-magical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/nature-is-magical/</guid>
      <description>Nature is Magical In a world dominated by the empirical and the logical, there exists a realm of enchantment just beyond our grasp, within the embrace of nature itself. The profound allure of nature transcends mere science, speaking to something deeper within us.
From the vibrant and ephemeral hues of a sunrise to the fascinating dance of fireflies in the moonlit night, the natural world whispers secrets that stir our souls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Sanctuaries; Rediscovering Our Bond with Earth</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/nature-sanctuaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/nature-sanctuaries/</guid>
      <description>Nature Sanctuaries: Rediscovering Our Bond with Earth Amidst bustling cities and modern landscapes, pristine pockets of nature remain, offering solace to weary souls seeking comfort. These sanctuaries, whether hidden urban oases or remote wilderness retreats, are where the beauty of the natural world flourishes.
From the serene stillness of ancient forests to the vibrant energy of coral reefs, these places remind us of our intrinsic connection with Earth. Venturing beyond the familiar, we discover the true treasures nature has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Humans Are Not the Enemy</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/humans-are-not-the-enemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/humans-are-not-the-enemy/</guid>
      <description>Humans Are Not the Enemy Nature is Magical While humanity&amp;rsquo;s impact on the environment is undeniable, painting humans as the sole enemy overlooks the potential for positive change. Inherent in us is the power to heal, restore, and protect. Through innovation, collaboration, and conscious choices, we can heal the scars on Earth&amp;rsquo;s surface and foster harmonious coexistence with nature.
By recognizing our capacity for positive impact, we embark on a journey towards ecological harmony and a shared future where humanity is a force for good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Endangered; The Extinction of Species and Its Impact on Our World</title>
      <link>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/endangered-the-extincion-of-species/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva-cali.vercel.app/post/2023/oct/endangered-the-extincion-of-species/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Species Vulnerability: We analyze in detail the endangered species and the factors pushing them to the edge of extinction. From habitat loss to human interference, we examine how our daily actions impact the living beings that share this world with us.
The Food Web: A Delicate Balance: We uncover the intricate food web that sustains life on Earth. Every species, no matter how small or large, plays a vital role in the ecosystem&amp;rsquo;s balance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
