<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Positiva - Echo notes &#43; news</title>
    <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Positiva - Echo notes &#43; news</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://positiva.netlify.app/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to become a better human</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/how-to-become-a-better-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/how-to-become-a-better-human/</guid>
      <description>How to Become a Better Human Becoming a better human involves a constant quest for self-improvement, not only for our own sake but for the collective good. Embracing empathy, practicing mindfulness, and cultivating kindness are just a few steps on this transformative journey. Through introspection and action, we delve into the practices that allow us to transcend our limitations and make meaningful contributions to the world around us.
Embrace Empathy: One of the cornerstones of becoming a better human is cultivating empathy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature is Magic</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/nature-is-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/nature-is-magic/</guid>
      <description>Nature is Magic In a world dominated by the empirical and the logical, a realm of enchantment lies just beyond our grasp—within the embrace of nature itself. Nature&amp;rsquo;s profound allure transcends mere science, speaking to something deeper within us. From the vibrant, ephemeral hues of a sunrise to the mesmerizing dance of fireflies in the moonlit night, the natural world whispers secrets that stir our souls. It is as if the very fabric of existence holds threads of enchantment that weave through the tapestry of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Positiva is the new positive</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/positiva-is-the-new-positive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/positiva-is-the-new-positive/</guid>
      <description>Positiva is the new positive In a world driven by change, positivity emerges as a guiding light. As we navigate the complexities of modern living, it&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that every small action has the potential to create a significant impact.
Finding Balance At the heart of our journey is the pursuit of ecological harmony. We believe that positivity can be channeled into sustainability, and that each step toward a greener world is a step toward a brighter future.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
