<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>markdown on Positiva - Echo notes &#43; news</title>
    <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/tags/markdown/</link>
    <description>Recent content in markdown on Positiva - Echo notes &#43; news</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://positiva.netlify.app/tags/markdown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Markdown ?</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/overpopulation-is-a-myth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/overpopulation-is-a-myth/</guid>
      <description>The concept of overpopulation has long been a subject of debate, often accompanied by doomsday predictions of resource scarcity and ecological collapse. However, a closer examination of demographic trends and consumption patterns reveals a more nuanced reality. The narrative of overpopulation overlooks the progress made in areas such as education and access to contraception. Addressing global challenges requires a holistic understanding that goes beyond simplistic population equations, prompting us to focus on sustainable practices and equitable resource distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Syntax</title>
      <link>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/nature-for-new-generations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>lucfreelance@gmail.com (Lucfreelance)</author>
      <guid>https://positiva.netlify.app/post/2023/ago/nature-for-new-generations/</guid>
      <description>Nature for New Generations The legacy of nature is an inheritance we pass down to the generations that follow. In an age dominated by screens and virtual experiences, how do we instill a deep love and appreciation for the natural world in the hearts of our youth? This article explores the importance of introducing children to the wonders of nature, fostering an understanding that goes beyond textbooks, and creating stewards who will protect our planet&amp;rsquo;s future.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
